https://posquote.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to footer
Retail
BarLiquor StorePizza ParlorConvenience StoreGrocery StoreSupermarket
Other
BreweryCar WashFurniture StoreAuto RepairComputer RepairDeli
Vendor ReviewsHardwareBlogSearch this website
Privacy Policy
Last updated: March 12, 2019
POS Quote (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the POS Quote website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://posquote.com
Contents1 Information Collection And Use2 Log Data3 Cookies4 Service Providers5 Security6 Links To Other Sites7 Children’s Privacy8 Compliance With Laws9 Changes To This Privacy Policy10 Contact Us10.0.1 POS Quote Team10.0.2 Latest posts by POS Quote Team (see all)
Information Collection And Use
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:
Name
Email address
Telephone number
Address
Log Data
We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.
Compliance With Laws
We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
The following two tabs change content below.BioLatest Posts
POS Quote Team
The staff at POSQuote.com is composed of industry professionals, experts, and current business owners. Through extensive research, we compile buyer's guides and review the best POS systems in the industry.
Latest posts by POS Quote Team (see all)
How to Sell a Restaurant: Your Step-by-Step Guide - August 21, 2020
The Best Restaurant Opening and Closing Checklist for 2020 - August 13, 2020
Risks in POS Systems: The Importance of a Security Assessment - January 9, 2020
Ready to get started? Call us at 1-800-715-2435!
Choosing a POS system can be a difficult decision, but we're here to assist you. We don't just review POS
systems; we provide complete buyer's guides that are tailored to your business type. Reach out to us to
see how we've helped more than 5,000 business owners with POS solutions!
© 2019-2020 | POS Quote™. Your Point of Sale Pros. All rights reserved.
